Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - Audiovisual material
    - Audiorecordings
      - (Th) Side A: Chester Stock/Sloan Kettering; Side B: Gary Hahn (?), W.U. Christian Vanguard, Bob Graham $1,000, GSL re Gus Adolfus letter, 1975 Sept 18-19; 135.6.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: GSL, Heilstand, Cheater Stock, ELS, Dean Burke; Side B: Dr. Dean Burk, GSL re 45%, CF Wojik, Robert Clark of Australia, 1975 Sept 19-20; 135.6.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Robert Clark, Henry David, Poly Kusch, Mrs. Lanning, Mike Culbert; Side B: Culbert, Robert Clark-Australia, Mrs. Hoff, Robert Clark, Laurie Thor, 1975 Sept 20-21; 135.6.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: EE Wooley [illegible], Robert Clarkson Kusch Letter, NY Warder, Robert Clark; Side B: Clark, GSL, M 135 re Ford Assn and Burt Dan's and Dr. Lic, Culbert, Hartm of Mr. Jones, HF Weyher, 1975 Sept 21-24; 135.6.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th, T202) Side A: M.C. & Al Wang, GSL re Gilkey Theologian Letter, Syl Jones, Al Wang, Goldman Jerrold Electronics; Side B: Mose Durst, Beyers office, Culbert, Mrs. L, L. Gilkey, Coors, Renata Herton, Coors Lindaas, 1975 Sept 24-26; 135.6.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Jones, Bob, H.F.W., Syl Jones (Medicine); Side B: Syl Jones, Bill Loeb, Joe Coors, MC, Geo Harman, IBM Tom Waring, Bob Beyers, GSL, 1975 Sept 24-26; 135.6.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Tennant Bryan, Geo Harman, U of Minn(?) Boysen, Boysen Polygraph, ACS, Willians ACSI, GSL on Press Release; Side B: GSL, Tennant Bryan, Peterson Res, IBM Dawson, Peterson of Gustavas, IBM Shuder, Coors Lawyer, Robert A Peterson, 1975 Sept 26-27; 135.6.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: R.A. Peterson, AP Minnepolis, UP, GSL, RA Peterson, GSL; Side B: GSL, GSL re TV culls, CBS D.C., Bill Loeb, Renata Heston, Mrs. Gover and Barbaum, KSTP, Thomas Gover, 1975 Sept 27-28; 135.6.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Prof. Thomas Gover, Ian Barbour I.B. Rgt, Star(?) Trib of Minneapolis; Side B: John Addington, Star Tribune, 1975 Sept 28; 135.6.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: GSL re S-T, Bob Beyers, BPPA, Prof Vikner; Side B: Bob Beters, Mrs. Peterson, Story in Minneapolis Tribune, TV Stationsand Willians Polygraph, GSL re Syl, D. Giannitrapony(?), 1975 Sept 28-Oct 9; 135.7.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (PC, R) Press Conference - Syl Jones Side A: Syl Jones Interview, Press Conf. Airport, Nobel Conf.; Side B: Joe Blade Star (pre Kiwanis talk), 1975 Sept 30; 135.7.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (L, T) W=S Cre. Fail. Meth, Kiwanis, Great Deb.; Side A: Kiwanis Interviews, Kiwanis Minister IQ vs soul, President reads Sharp, Door closed; Side B: W=S end, Great Debate, Gus Adolf, Creat. Fail Method, 1975 Sept 30; 135.7.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (L) Side A: 2nd Lecture, Take 1 or 3 Bob and Mark, Diagram, Thanks B&M; Side B: transoprep (?), Admin Lounge with Green, 1975 Sept 30; 135.7.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (L) W=S, Panel 2 cont.; Side A: Panel Members; Side B: Glenn Seaburgans, 1975 Sept 30-Oct 1; 135.7.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (N,C) Side A: News re ply(?), NBC news W=S, Steve Chain, City Mag SF; Side B: Chain cont., 1975 Oct 1-2; 135.7.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (N, C) Side A: Glenn Seaburg WFS, IB, W=S, Lipman; Side B: Elvee and Gilkey, 1975 Oct 2; 135.7.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (N, C) Side A: Pam, Lipman, Barbour, G.S., W=S talking; Side B: IB & FL, Ian Barbour, W=S, Adj, W=S responds to questions, 1975 Oct 2; 135.7.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (T, L) Duffus, Great Debate, W=S Session, Dick; Side A: W=S Session, Dick Duffus, Pierre Burton show; Side B: blank, 1975 Oct 2-3; 135.7.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (C, T) Syl Jones, HFW, RKG $; Side A: Great Debate, Heston, Frank Ragone, Lemard Goldman, E.E.; Side B: H.F.W., RKG off, Dianne Schuck, L.O. Swanson, RKG - Graham SU $, Mrs. Syl, Syl Jones, 1975 Oct 3; 135.7.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (C, T) Goldman, GSL, Syl Jones on Jehovah Witness; Side A: Syl Jones, Swanson; Side B: Syl Jones, Leonard Goldman re arrival, GSL, 1975 Oct 3-4; 135.7.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (C, T) Toronto Customs, Mrs. Wolley Goldman Family; Side A: Mrs. Woolley, Leo Goldman and family, L.G., EE Wooley; Side B: EE Wooley, Great Debate, EE Wooley, Robt. Price, Kiwanis, Toronto Customs, 1975 Oct 4-7; 135.8.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (C, T) Tor. AAL S.F. Kitty Denke; Side A: Great Debate, Price Minnie Kiwanis, Polygraph, Rehearsal, Dianne Schuck, Richard Gillman, John Jurens, Rehearsal #2; Side B: Kitty Denke, 1975 Oct 7-8; 135.8.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Giannitrapani (?), GSL re Syl, HFW, Syl Jones; Side B: J. Oppenheimer, J Ocent (?), Sharpie sale, Frank Jerrald, 1975 Oct 9-12; 135.8.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Frank Ragone, Joe Walty, Syl Jones re $ and deal; Side B: Syl Jones, B. Oliver, JEC, HFW, Israel, Novotny, Dennis Rorve(?), 1975 Oct 12-17; 135.8.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Jack Kroft, Hoover, Giannatrapani; Side B: Giannatrapani, GSL re Coore (?) letter, Tennent Bryan on Polygraph and Nixon Letter, 1975 Oct 17-20; 135.8.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Tennant Bryan, Tom Waring, Jenk(?) Jones, Hal P., Jack Knabt, Dick Shockley; B Side: Dick Shockley, Coors, BPPA JJ Smith, Coors, Wrong Number, U of Michigan, Norman Lopatai(?) re 11 Feb 1976, 1975 Oct 20-22; 135.8.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Norman Lopatin, U of Kansas, Miller, Tulsa, Wichita, Sharpie Show, Torregrossa, Barton Patrolmen's (?); Side B: JJ Smith, HFW, Technim, Lopatin U of Michigan, LoPatin read MS, Proctor Jones re wine test, 1975 Oct 22-24; 135.8.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Ed. David, MBS, Ed. D, Ann McGuire, Fricke; Side B: Fricke, GSL, Loma Linda, Hoyt, USC Student Union, Dashoff USC, 1975 Oct 24-28; 135.8.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (C) Taxi Weil (Gen Inst), AAL SF->NY Elston GE; Side A: AAL Clerks Elston GE; Side B: Im Taxi, Weil, 1975 Oct 24-25; 135.8.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: USC, Dassoff, Syl Jones, Loma Linda Assoc Prof Gary Ross (7th day); Side B: Prof. Gary Ross, Syl Jones re KU and 17 Nov., Sears, Mike Culbert about misc, 1975 Oct 28-29; 135.8.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: Sears, Bell Cook - Newsweek, Univ Texas, Nored, UTexas, GSL; Side B: GSL cont., SU Acct, Ann McGuire, WN W=S, HFW, U of Michigan, GSL re SCI.L.Ed(?), Mary Ann Hauck, 1975 Oct 29-31; 135.8.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - (Th) Side A: M.A. Howick(?), Dr. Frieman, ARJ, Berieter re Israel, Wachburr; Side B: Miels, U of K, U of Texas, Syl Jones, JR Pierce re NAS, 1975 Oct 31-Nov 3; 135.8.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 135)
      - 1975 Nov 30-Dec 16, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1975 Dec 16 - 1976 Jan 7, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Jan 7-26, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Jan 26 - Feb 5, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Feb 5-13, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Feb 13-22, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Feb 22 - Mar 10, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Mar 9 - Apr 2, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Apr 2-13, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Apr 13-26, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 Apr 26 - May 7, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 May 7-16, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 145)
      - 1976 May 13-20, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 May 20-31, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 May 31 - Jun 10, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Jun 10 - Jul 13, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Jul 13 - Aug 26, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Aug 26 - Sep 9, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Sep 9 - Oct 5, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Oct 5-24, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Oct 24 - Nov 15, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Nov 15 - Dec 9, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1976 Dec 9 - 1977 Jan 27, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1977 Jan 27 - March 7, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 146)
      - 1977 Mar 7 - Apr 11, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Mar 30 - May 24, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 May 24 - Jul 18, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Jul 18 - Aug 15, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Aug 15 - Sep 20, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Sep 20 - Oct 26, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Oct 26 - Dec 5, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1977 Dec 5 - 1978 Jan 16, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1978 Jan 13- Mar 8, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1978 Mar 6 - Jun 20, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1978 Jun 14 - Jul 31, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - 1978 Jul 31 - Sep 8, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 147)
      - Robt. Whiteside / Robt. Cancro, 1971 Feb 7-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Mar 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Mar 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club / Ken Lehner, 1971 Mar 21-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Mar 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Apr 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - TV - Schockley AM Dunbar, 1971 May 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Monday Conference Duke Waddell, 1971 May 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 May 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Lecture, 1971 May 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Lecture, 1971 May 29-30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Lecture, 1971 May 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Lecture, 1971 May 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley -Watt Debate-Lecture, 1971 Jun 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 24-Jul 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jun 24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Owen Spann Show (W.S.), 1971 Jun 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jul 1, 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jul 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jul 15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley - Culbert, 1971 Jun 21 - Jul 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jul 15, 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Jul 22, Aug 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Aug 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Aug 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Aug 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Aug 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Sep 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Sep 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Sep 23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Sep 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Oct 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Oct 21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Nov 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Thur Three Club, 1971 Nov 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices, 1971 May; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices, 1972 Apr 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Diffusion on Grain Boundary, 1972 May 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Mag. Bubbles, 1972 Jun 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - General Intro (1&2 of 3), 1974 Apr 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - General Intro (3 of 3), 1974 Apr 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - S. Norrman w/ Prof. Garrett Hardin, 1972 Aug 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices, 1976 Apr 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices, 1976 Apr 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Path Conc. J. Transistor, 1976 Apr 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Path Conc. J. Transistor, 1976 Apr 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Grain Boundary and Dislocation, 1976 May 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Grain Boundary (conference with Shapiro), 1976 May 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Shockley Reminices - Dislocation Motion, GB Energy, Diff GB, 1976 May 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - TATIT, 1976 May 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - Magnetic Domains and Bubbles, 1975 Jun 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - EE 200 (How Invented), 1976 May 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - 1980 March 5, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 148)
      - 1968-1976, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - 1968-1974, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - 1975, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - 1974-1975, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - 1976, 12 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Final Exam Tape, 1976 June; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - EE 327B Final, 1973 June; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Telephone Recordings, 1970; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Unlabeled Tape, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Tape - Litterman and Sanfield, 1972; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - National Institute for Trial Advocacy, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Tape - Ed Jackson, 1970 Feb 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - The Greaseman - Sampler of Racial Humor, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Skip Greeby - Coin-Tossing, 1971 Aug 23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Al Wang, Conference, 1971 Apr 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Wright - Shockley, 1971 Aug 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #1, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #3, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #4, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #5, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #6, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Coin Tossing #7, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Tapes on Research, 1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Various Lecture and Telephone Tapes, 1968-1971; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 149)
      - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 169)
      - Edited by KDVS Davis Campus U of C, 1971 Nov 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 169)
    - Georgia Center for Continuing Education/WGTV VT-587 video, 1973-1974; Check for possible copies on other media. Hoover has all Firing Line programs (however, they have dated this program, S0145 "Shockley's Thesis", as 6/10/1974 instead of 6/10/1973). Fairly strong vinegar smell. SMPL estimates approx. $500 for outsourced transfer (Box 75)
      2" videotape containing WS on Firing Line 6/10/1973, "Research Taboos #101" Shockley Debate 3/15/74 and several other probably non-WS recordings
    - Data Cartridges
      - (1) Good Tape Unformatted - Full Backup, 1987 Sep 16; 128.001 (Box 128)
      - (2) Microage MV - Weekly to Supplim't Cart 3, 1987 Sep 18; 128.002 (Box 128)
      - (3) Back up since 1987 Nov 20, 128.003 (Box 128)
      - (4) Full Back Up, 1987 Nov 20; 128.004 (Box 128)
      - (5) Full Rip - Verify LBL B5KP4 Starts, 1988 Jun 26; 128.005 (Box 128)
      - (6) B6KP1 - Full Back Up, 1988 Sep 5; 128.006 (Box 128)
      - (7) B7KP1 - Full, 1988 Sep 8; 128.007 (Box 128)
      - (8) NG Sony - Mag Erase & Selective Backup of 26 files, 1988 Sep-Dec; 128.008 (Box 128)
      - (9) B9KP2 & 2.5, 1988 Nov 10 - 1989 Jan 1; 128.009 (Box 128)
      - (10) B10KP1, 2, & 3 - ATT Diary, 128.010 (Box 128)
      - (11) New - W. Shockley - Full Backup, 1988 Dec 4; 128.011 (Box 128)
      - (12) 1st = D: B12KP2 HT (Should be KP1)/ 2nd = C: B12KP2 HL (Should be KP2), 1989 Jan 31; 128.012 (Box 128)
      - (13) No Title, 1989 Feb (1)6; 128.013 (Box 128)
      - (12 NG) For Prompt Failure #223, 1989 Feb 12; 128.014 (Box 128)
    - Films
      - Original negative of Shockley's time at Cal Tech, 1962; 104.1; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 104)
        35 mm original negative film about Shockley's time at Cal Tech. Letter included from "Jack". The film is copied from nitrate film.
      - Folder for Letter, 104.2 (Box 104)
      - Dr. Schockley Clips from Cal Tech - Footage Picture, 1962; 104.3; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 104)
      - Tokyo TV - Reel 1, 1963; 104.4; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 104)
      - Tokyo TV - Reel 2, 1963; 104.5; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 104)
      - Dom, Quinn Air Check, 1971 Sep 11; 120.001; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 120)
      - 10.6 vi 81, 120.006; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 120)
    - Saga of a Sperm Bank Baby / Al DiFante and the Recipients (Kayden DM 1953), 1980 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      7" 45 rpm record sent to WS via Phil Donahue (following his appearance on the program about his sperm donation)
    - Video recordings
      - "Quark" - Germinal Choice, 1986 Oct 28; 109.001; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic S) (Box 109)
        Includes a letter from Gul Seden Wines; a copy of the "Quark" episode which examined the issues surrounding Dr. Graham's Germinal Choice project as it aired in Italy during the 1985 season.
      - "Repub. Nomination - Quayle & Bush", 1988 Apr 1 - Aug 18; 109.002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - DB + 60' & David Brinkley, 1983; 109.003; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - 6A5 Video, 1986 Jan 5-6; 109.004; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Video Tape ID: 6A5 (from Shockley's ID system) Contains material from various shows Includes a time chart for the clips (Box 109)
      - RS1, 109.005; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Rebecca, 1984 Nov 10; 109.006; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Moyers: Crisis Black Amer./ Ted Knight & John O'Conner, 1986 Jan 25; 109.007; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Includes a time chart for the clips (Box 109)
      - People Are Talking - WS & Weking, 1984 Oct 15; 109.008; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - No Title, 1985 Dec 12; 109.009; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Includes time chart for clips (Box 109)
      - No Title, 109.010; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - ELS Tmp., circa 1980s; 109.011; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Includes list of clips ELS Personal = ELS Tmp (Box 109)
      - DREW 4, circa 1980s; 109.012; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Women of Substance - Ch 2, 1984 Sep 10-15; 109.013; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - RS2, 109.014; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - French TV/ Stray Dog, 1983 Dec 22-23; 109.015; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - C.R. Mollenhoff Deposition, 109.016; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Copy from beta tapes (Box 109)
      - 1 Year Old, 109.017; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - SPELL Bound - [Mrgry?] Peeh Myrid Blyman/ [Lihehine - Misc. Supy?]/ Raiders Football, 109.018; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Excerpts from the Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, 109.019; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); From the Communication Center Video Library (Box 109)
      - Nate on NY Crime, 1984 Jan 15; 109.020; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Wallenberg Off./ Mandeilne, 1987 Dec 6-20; 109.021; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Hanna at 10 Months Old - Copy, 109.022; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - No Title, 1988 May 1; 109.023; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - No Title, 109.024; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Boston #3, 1984 Oct 19; 109.025; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - At about '85 to go, bad spots caused by hotter [adjustments?], 1983 Dec 26; 109.026; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); Tape that jammed [bides?] pick-up at ~182. NEW F.B. there Includes card of information (Box 109)
      - Ch 32 - Thru the Genetic mage (Transcript $), 1983 Dec 31; 109.027; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Dr. Shockley, 109.028; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - AWT #2 - WS on Nightwatch, 1984 Sep 30 - Oct 1; 109.029; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - W. Shockley, 1984 Oct 17; 109.030; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Leakey, KQED, 1983 Nov 23-27; 109.031; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Rep. Primary, 1982 May 14; 109.032; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
        Badly damaged on the right side
      - Graid William Son - Tambu/ Superbowl, 1987 Jan 25; 109.033; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Save Reagan to Congress, 1985 Nov 21; 109.034; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 109)
      - Brinkley & The Day After, 1983 Nov 20; 109.035; 1 videotape(s) (vhs); see home diary (Box 109)
      - Dr. W. Shockley, 120.007; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 120)
      - TK Scart, 1954 Jul 17; 120.008; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 120)
      - Copy of Deposition of Clark R. Mollenhoff - Tape 1 of 2, 1983 Oct 31; 120.021; 1 videotape(s) (beta) (Box 120)
      - Copy of Deposition of Clark R. Mollenhoff - Tape 2 of 2, 1983 Oct 31; 120.022; 1 videotape(s) (beta) (Box 120)
      - William Shockley - 857-1378, 1982 May 14; 125.001; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 125)
      - Semi-Conductor Giants #3: The Integrated Circuit, 125.002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 125)
      - Viewpoint - Intelligence re. W. Shockley, 1977 Nov 9-26; 125.003; 1 videotape(s) (1 inch) (Box 125)
      - N.W. Ayer Incorporated AT&T Communications/ Corporate - Nobel Prize, circa 1950s; 125.004; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 125)
      - SF 30-124, undated; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 149)
      - SF 60-124, undated; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 149)
      - KDVS at UC Davis From Tom Jacob, 1972 Jan 31; 1 videotape reel(s) (Box 169)
    - Record of Army Bumper Missile Launching, 1956 Dec 27; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 112)
    - 8-in Floppy Disk w/ W=S 2, 1 computer media (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Unlabeled reels (Box 182)
  - Awards, medals, plaques, certificates, souvenirs, 1956-1986 (Box 69-70, 74, 172)